<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>kwave.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Kwave</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Kwave</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Kwave</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Kwave</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Kwave</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Kwave</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Kwave</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Kwave</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Kwave</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKwavexx</name>
  <summary>Kwave is a sound editor designed for the KDE Desktop Environment</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Kwave is a sound editor designed for the KDE Desktop Environment</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">KWave is een geluidsbewerker ontworpen voor de KDE bureaubladomgeving</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Kwave jest edytorem zbudowanym dla Środowiska Pulpitu KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">O Kwave é um editor de som desenhado para o Ambiente de Trabalho KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Kwave é um editor de som desenvolvido para o KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Kwave je editor zvuku navrhnutý pre KDE pracovné prostredie</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Kwave är en ljudeditor konstruerad för KDE:s skrivbordsmiljö</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Kwave — звуковий редактор, створений для стільничного середовища KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxKwave is a sound editor designed for the KDE Desktop Environmentxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      With Kwave you can record, play back, import and edit many sorts of audio files including multi channel files.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">With Kwave you can record, play back, import and edit many sorts of audio files including multi channel files.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Met Kwave kunt u vele soorten audiobestanden opnemen, afspelen, importeren en bewerken inclusief multi-channel bestanden.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Dzięki Kwave możesz nagrywać, odtwarzać, importować i edytować wiele różnych plików dźwiękowych uwzględniając w tym pliki wielokanałowe.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Com o Kwave, poderá gravar, reproduzir, importar e editar diversos tipos de ficheiros de áudio, incluindo ficheiros multi-canais.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Com o Kwave, você pode gravar, reproduzir, importar e editar diversos tipos de arquivos de áudio, incluindo arquivos multicanais.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Man kan spela in, spela upp, importera och redigera många sorters ljudfiler, inklusive filer med flera kanaler, med Kwave.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">За допомогою Kwave ви можете записувати, відтворювати, імпортувати та редагувати файли звукових даних багатьох типів, зокрема файли з багатоканальним звуком.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxWith Kwave you can record, play back, import and edit many sorts of audio files including multi channel files.xx</p>
    <p>
      Kwave includes some plugins to transform audio files in several ways and presents a graphical view with a complete zoom- and scroll capability.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Kwave includes some plugins to transform audio files in several ways and presents a graphical view with a complete zoom- and scroll capability.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Kwave bevat enige plug-ins om geluidsbestanden op verschillenden manieren te transformeren en biedt een grafische weergave met de mogelijkheid van volledig te zoomen en te schuiven.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Kwave zawiera kilka wtyczek do przekształcania plików dźwiękowych na różne sposoby i do przedstawiania widoku graficznego z możliwością jego powiększania i przewijania.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Kwave inclui alguns 'plugins' para transformar os ficheiros de áudio de diversas formas e apresenta uma vista gráfica com uma capacidade completa de ampliação e deslocamento.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">O Kwave inclui alguns plugins para transformar os arquivos de áudio de diversas formas e apresenta um visual gráfico com capacidade completa zoom e deslocamento.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Kwave inkluderar några insticksmoduler för att omvandla ljudfiler på flera sätt, och visar en grafisk vy med fullständig zoom- och panoreringsförmåga.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">До складу Kwave включено декілька додатків для перетворення звукових даних. Передбачено графічне представлення дати із усіма можливостями масштабування та гортання.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKwave includes some plugins to transform audio files in several ways and presents a graphical view with a complete zoom- and scroll capability.xx</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">http://kwave.sourceforge.net/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">http://sourceforge.net/bugs/?group_id=6478</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>http://kwave.sourceforge.net/screenshot/kwave-gui-tab.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>kwave</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
